<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Nagkumarです</title>
      <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Nagkumarです</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>■ The Aparātāntrik Analysis Of Vedā-s – Trikaśāsana Viewpoint. ■</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Trikashasan/trikashasana-viewpoint/The-Apar%C4%81t%C4%81ntrik-Analysis-Of-Ved%C4%81-s-%E2%80%93-EN</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Trikashasan/trikashasana-viewpoint/The-Apar%C4%81t%C4%81ntrik-Analysis-Of-Ved%C4%81-s-%E2%80%93-EN</guid>
    <description>Bhārat is a country of unity in diversity. From ancient times, various streams of knowledge and science have been flooding here. Vedā-s, Upaniṣads, Purānā-s, Vedānga-s and Ādhibhautik spiritual sciences have been flowing here in the tradition of study and teaching in their entirety.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>■ वेदोंका अपरतंत्रीक विश्लेषण — त्रिक शासन दृष्टिकोन. ■</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Trikashasan/trikashasana-viewpoint/The-Apar%C4%81t%C4%81ntrik-Analysis-Of-Ved%C4%81-s</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Trikashasan/trikashasana-viewpoint/The-Apar%C4%81t%C4%81ntrik-Analysis-Of-Ved%C4%81-s</guid>
    <description>भारतवर्ष अनेकता में एकता का देश है। अति प्राचीन काल से ही विभिन्न ज्ञानविज्ञान की धारायें भारतभूमि को आप्यायित करती आ रही हैं। वेद, उपनिषद्, पुराण, वेदाङ्ग एवं आधिभौतिक आध्यात्मिक ...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>an introduction to trikaśāsan [tāntrik philosophy]</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/trikashasan/trikashasan-introduction-en</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/trikashasan/trikashasan-introduction-en</guid>
    <description>The stream of Bhāratiya knowledge and practice has been flowing in two forms, Vedik and Āgama. If the root of the Vedik flow is the exhalation of Vāmdeva, one of the mouths of Lord Swachchandanātha Bhairava, then the root of the Āgamaic or Tāntrik flow is the speech of the five mouths of Lord Swachchandanātha Bhairava, and the Bhairavāgamadhārā (Bhairavāgamik flow)—eternal; indifference; is free and secret; And this stream is always implemented by the spontaneous grace of Lord Swachchandanātha Bhairava.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>“त्रिकशासन” (तन्त्र दर्शन): एक परिचय.</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/trikashasan/trikashasan-introduction</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/trikashasan/trikashasan-introduction</guid>
    <description>भारतीय ज्ञान एवं साधना की धारा वैदिक और आगम दो रूपों में प्रवाहित होती आ रही है। वैदिक प्रवाह का मूल यदि भगवान् स्वच्छंदनाथ भैरवजी के एक मुख वामदेव का उच्छ्वास है, तो आगमिक या तान्त्रिक ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>who are we?</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/about-us</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/about-us</guid>
    <description>hail, noble seeker, and welcome to the sacred domain of karpurgauram! we, a group of humble fellowship of devotees &amp; volunteers, have embarked upon a most reverent quest—to unveil ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>internal posture</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Practices/internal-posture</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Practices/internal-posture</guid>
    <description>Now I shall speak to you about the conquest of Internal Posture. This is to get established at the junction—the middle or the meeting point of the two breaths.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>schools of kashmir shaivism</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/kashmir-shaivism/schools-of-kashmir-shaivism</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/kashmir-shaivism/schools-of-kashmir-shaivism</guid>
    <description>Kashmir Shaivism is known as the Pure Trika System. The word Trika means “the threefold science of man and his world.” In the idea of trika, there are three Śakti-s (energies): parā (supreme), aparā (lowest), and parāpara (combination of the lowest and the highest).</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>purity of mind</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Practices/purity-of-mind</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Practices/purity-of-mind</guid>
    <description>—Śuddhacitt &amp; Āsana— —Swami Lakshamanjoo— ∫Sunday, May 4, 1980∫ Purity of mind is the first requisite for spiritual practice. If the mind is free from attachment and detachment, love and hatred, praise and blame, it can remain stable; and then it is termed a clean mind.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>krama</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/krama/krama</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/krama/krama</guid>
    <description>]■[ “Krama System.” ]■[ ⎯ The Krama system does not recognize the ways of either the Pratyabhijna or the Kula system. In the Krama system, you must rise in succession, step by step.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>kula</title>
    <link>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/kula-akula/kula</link>
    <guid>https://karpurgauram.xyz/Introduction/kula-akula/kula</guid>
    <description>]■[ “Kula System.” ]■[ ⎯ The Kula system teaches you how you can live in caitanya (universal Consciousness), the real nature of yourself, in the act of ascending and descending ...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>